FROM ID COACH TO COACHFACE™
In 2009, inventor and entrepreneur Isaac Daniel introduced ID Coach in Tampa, Florida.
During Super Bowl week, athletes, coaches, media and football executives witnessed the future.
The system securely transmitted play calls directly from coaches to designated players.
Military-grade encryption replaced hand signals and traditional audio transmitters.
Strategic decisions could move instantly and securely during competition.
The technology was futuristic. The sports world was not yet ready.
But the vision endured: better tools, better decisions, better performance.
More than fifteen years later, that vision has evolved.
CoachFace™ measures coaching intelligence, accountability and performance.
Fans can evaluate, predict, rank and challenge the decisions that shape sports.
IF FANS KNOW WHAT COACHES SHOULD DO, CAN THEY OUTPERFORM THEM?